I've been preparing for this for a
little while now and I've also all that
noise all that noise
we got here another message please say
is from Mum Bonus Time I don't think I
could take another message is not for
mumbo alright appreciate ya get rid of
this oh my oh my goodness
alright whoa to my old chum rockets of
reunion her g1 anvils oh my goodness
what a gift I definitely do need anvils
and rockets of reunion that's like
that's like the fork of friendship right
that's gonna be mumbo Oh mumbo okay so I
know exactly why he's put this here and
why it says appreciate ya it's not
because I sent him the carrots or the
endless text messages like a needy
girlfriend no no no no no this is for
something that actually happened off
camera so I'm gonna have to explain so I
saw mumbo over here was working on his
base which is actually looking in sane
insane like he puts my house a little
bit to shame cuz this is like wow wow
wow wow wow wow he's embraced the
diagonals it's in wonderful proportion
good job mumbo it's very different to my
base which is sort of more of a
structure rather than the giant mega
base sort of thing so they're very
different but my goodness my little bit
jealous of this but what I saw was mumbo
standing here afk for a really long time
and I was like hmm I wonder if he knows
he's afk and then in the chat it said
mumbo has died to a skeleton so I was
like okay he was definitely FK so I
literally just came over here popped all
his stuff in here which he's now filled
up with with jungle stuff and then he
came back like two hours later and he
was like oh my God thank you so much so
I think that is why he's given me that
and honestly I really really needed that
diamond block I have absolutely zero
diamonds I'm gonna need it for all the
dark prism rain anyway I have prepared a
whole bunch of materials for this this
build so I'm I'm ready
to get started on this thing and have
this hopefully mostly done let's just
let's just crack on get this done
straight away let's start the time lapse
[Music]
well it's not entirely complete because
there are some parts like here which
look a bit odd without anything on the
top and there's actually a few more
towers that need to be put in but I am
again out of dark prismarine and in fact
I'm so out of dark prismarine that in
the shopping district I couldn't even
afford to pay for what I used so I have
actually given impulse an IOU
which is a very dangerous thing to do on
the hermit craft server because an IOU
could be used at any point for any means
so I may come to regret that I am loving
it so far myself I've really enjoyed
building it and I'm looking forward
thoroughly to seeing it completely
finished I didn't quite realize just how
many blocks I was gonna need maybe I
should have done some mathematics but at
the moment this build is a pretty face
and not a lot else because at the back
there's still nothing absolutely nothing
and you can get an idea for just how
much I'm going to need in order to
complete this project
not to mention all of the training that
I'm gonna have to do in the future but
since that is about as far as we can get
with the build for today we might as
well crack on with trying to get some
more diamonds I am again out of diamonds
for real
no more diamonds at all so we need to do
a bit of market research I'm not
entirely sure what shops are available
now I do need to open up one oh wow
big pile of diamonds I need to figure
out what shop I can make to make myself
some diamonds
so obviously the Guardian farm is taken
I have emptied it out and impulses have
clearly seen my IOU that was in there we
have a shelcha shop which is always a
big money spinner we have passed it on
which I'm not sure what this is at all
there's a log shop and already a rocket
shop which means yeah most of the money
spinners already gone books included
however I don't see a shop for some of
the more grinding materials such as sand
and gravel but what I'm thinking is we
could actually make a shop that's for
anything literally anything and it's
just whatever I have and that I'm
selling at the time but I don't actually
have the resources to sell at the moment
so we might have to go on a resource
gathering hunt in order to get there but
maybe next episode will open up a shop
but in the meantime I really want to
keep investing some time into this
there's bounties on people's heads PvP
only allowed cod heads Oh cut heads
again B's B dubs non PvP bounty 75
points do we really want to I think in
order to keep up because we are actually
really far behind now with crane crane
again Green is in 4th place yeah 265
points it's pretty good but 1st place is
currently on 843 so we've really got a
long way to go
so I guess I'm gonna have to pick up
this bouncy again back to the ocean we
go let's do this again finally the last
one ok that's 20 that took a little less
time than last time so I must have been
a bit lucky but there we are 20 cod
heads easy bounty there we go turn card
heads and check this out
scar has actually submitted five
different Hermit heads for 200 points
he's put under scar green so hopefully
Cleo knows that we're kind of teaming up
now that's 300 points right there just
on the bounties bringing us to a total
of 565 which will bring us into third
place man we're gonna we're making some
good progress here we just need to see
if we can get some more bounties
especially people like b-dubs
is he the only one who's non pvp no
there's a few noncom patterns tengo ren
bdub stress I have an idea is a bit
weird
but I'm pretty sure we can convince
these guys to give us their minecraft
head
winning this head hunt would certainly
help out with our diamond situation big
time so my idea is to convince those
people who are non PV peers to come over
here and basically just trade us their
heads for well whatever we can give them
and I actually have something that I
feel like I can give them and it is over
here I've been trading away with my new
and improved zombie villager breeder and
I have got a lot of gold and carrots so
this is definitely going in my shop but
I might be able to convince some Hermits
to give me their life in exchange for
some golden carrots but we need to do
this with a little bit of flair and I've
got a good idea for it what we will make
is a guillotine which should be a nice
visual way to hit to do this if I put
two string here can I make it so that
this is actually oh my goodness I can
this is gonna be awesome so here's the
plan we've got our guillotine our
minecraft guillotine at that and then we
get someone who's willing to trade us
their life and we get them to come here
we get them to go up the executioner
will then put them into position like
this they'll have to walk forward put
their head right about here and then the
the executioner removes the string boom
now obviously in order to get the
minecraft heads we actually have to beat
them in PvP this is really PvP but as
soon as those land we can then just pop
them on the head with the axe and they
[\h__\h] and then they should drop the my
craft head let's make a little pathway
up be great tip as well for when you're
building if you are using the path block
you can see there's like that little
line of dirt and it's really annoying if
you want your build to look that little
bit more finished just replace that
block there and doesn't that look so
much better sitting on there you can't
tell there's dirt under there well
that's that's because there isn't but
anyway just a little tip if you're
building
that little block can be such a pain a
neat scar to get on because I can't
exactly test this on my own I can get in
here and I could get myself lined up but
I don't have this the person to actually
remove the string to see if this will
work because the worst thing is if this
just like kills them with the anvils
then we won't get the minecraft heads
have no idea if this is actually gonna
work you know what I'm glad I did that
because that isn't that isn't in the
right place at all what am I thinking
there we go
I fixed it it doesn't look quite as good
but at least the anvils are gonna drop
in the right place now this is why
you've always got to test okay so when
scar gets on I'm going to make sure that
this works 100% before we actually
decide to use this but because scar
lives on the other side of the world to
me he may not be online for some time so
we might as well make ourselves useful
and start preparing some stock for my
shop for next episode so we're actually
going to go and prepare ourselves and
we're gonna go and get some sand and
gravel because everybody at some point
will need lots of it so let's go
grinding
[Music]
take a look at this gravel gravel
we got sand gravel galore this was yeah
this was great
what boss garden did Skaar just save me
from creepers huh we might make a we
might make a hero out of you yet Skaar
but look at this this is going to fuel
my shop I just need to come up with a
design for it I don't want to do what I
did last season which was just like a
traveling cart I need to come up with
something else
so I'll sleep on that one but for now
since Skaar is here I think it's time to
have a little conversation with him
about what we built over there earlier
he's just talking to himself he's just
like I help the bees left
no wait Skaar come back no come back
hello Skaar
whoa I've got to say your village is
looking absolutely magnificent ah you
just you're just melting my heart over
here thank you did you did you happen to
notice the the addition that I've made
you know after a long day's work I go to
bed and I wake up and the first thing I
see when I log on is the Sinister device
is this for me grand are you coming
after my beautiful wizard head
no no well it's not technically for you
it's for anyone that's like not in the
PvP for the head game we need that
bounty but I do need you to get on here
and test it because I am yeah I need any
two people so if you wouldn't mind okay
in the middle there right that yes yeah
yeah yeah that's it okay now we just
test this but but okay
how many how many hearts did you take I
took four hearts
we're hearts damage ouch and okay
alright little sharper there you got it
got it got to really get that on the
grindstone I have to I might have to use
the sword then in that case cuz that oh
right so this is for us to get people
see when all else pvp them right
technically speaking so we kind of need
them to to come in and
accept their fate you know so I'm
feeling like we can trade goods for
people to come here and use the
guillotine and then we can take their
heads now unfortunately because of the
way that it works we actually have to do
the final blow with the Diamondbacks or
the sword or whatever
we can't yeah we can't just like yeah if
they die from an anvil they wouldn't
drop the head so it's it's it's more of
a visual thing it's more of a ceremony
if you like it's more of a public
holiday Lupul yeah his Lupo is illusion
I like it this is gonna be fun who's our
first target well you see b-dubs has a
bounty on his head of 75 points and
monkey is online right now so if we can
convince him alright let's see if we can
go and find b-dubs do you know where his
house is absolutely not
alright this is gonna be fun I think
this is a good place to start seeing as
this portal says b-dubs 100 it says
redstone master I think this is the
wrong one I really know much about his
reading skills I'm guessing that he's he
doesn't know red stain
he's comparable to our skills okay yeah
like this fire round and see what is
this what is this what is going on here
wasn't there a giant goat here at one
point it lays on the floor no I didn't
see that it's something grant ler oh
that's so sad look at it look it's like
a tear coming down it's I Oh a fallen
goat doesn't look like beetles his hair
oh yeah literally I could just see him I
think that's him I just saw some
particles like out of render distance
where where's he's literally he's right
by he's like okay let me see me he's
yeah only a little little while away
look there is I see him I saw I saw
someone walking around in the render
distance it's a beautiful little house
over here and an even beautiful b-double
oh god don't go right up in his grill
okay you know we good at this that's
that's true but don't worry don't worry
I brought Wizards for it so we can sneak
away easier just let that sink into your
inventory there you go okay what's the
plan we got the whole crew here what's
what's the plan okay he's right he's
right we lay the bait we lay the bait
and we take him to the guillotine okay
all right listen okay look this this is
why this is why there's never any night
beam up just standing by his bed right
clicking like mad Ben he is so nervous
he doesn't know should we just like go
like see if you see if he takes see if
he takes the bait come on come on well
let me get some carrots out to look no
no no not too many we got a long way to
go scar we got a long way to go
I'm getting them I'm getting it invested
I'm getting them invested which way do
we go
so we go we're gonna do this a bit but
time at a time we're gonna take him all
the way back to the portal Carrie Carrie
is serious look at him look at him and
this is easy we should just some more
people I'm just dropping him on his head
okay where's the portal just here we
just create a nice line of carrots and
we gotta go
come let's go yeah I can't believe this
is working
oh look at it I'm imagining I imagine
like on beatab side I'm just hearing
like he's gonna have a lot of carrots
then yeah I mean he's not gonna he's not
gonna need to use it because we've given
him lots come on little buddy
can you move like 3,000 blocks in
seconds with golden carrots okay now he
now he sees the guillotine and he's like
[Laughter]
let's give a cool let's give him a cool
hi hey hi done thank you so much yeah
you like you like carrots I love carrots
especially the golden kind interview
with piece of candy trail do you wanna
add some more golden carrots like this
we've got a whole box of them in this
chest for you you do yeah hey holy cow
it comes at a price it comes at a price
you see this fancy here machine yeah
yeah yeah yeah we would like to offer
you the deal of the century see we need
okay your head you're fair you do yeah
okay we need it and we will give you a
box of carrots if you use the machine
okay use the Machine use the machine
it'll get my face what do you need my
face for magic magic if I if I do this I
get the carrots are you here the carrots
you just you just stand in it right
right there right there right here yes
damn right here oh we move that oh there
we go you're gonna do the honors go
oh no no no it's it's virtually painless
are you ready hold on hold on I need I
can't I can't
don't do this well you know I think my
head can be Deb's you hold that crystal
like no other hold on I got it I'm
holding on tight hold tight yeah ready
yeah yes okay did I do it yeah well you
win you won the box of carrots did you
get my face I don't know where I think
your face is somewhere oh he's got it
got him you've never looked so beautiful
oh why thank you wait you didn't like my
beard stuff went everywhere beat up just
like it's all over the place well I
think as a fair deal yeah we get to
clean the bounty on your head and you
get a box of carrots in the anvils to
pay if you want yeah you can keep all
right thanks meetups thank you
appreciate you do you know your way home
no okay well we'll see you later I'd say
I'd say that was pretty successful but I
wouldn't say it was I butchered him
I chopped him at least three times with
my sword as far as the guillotine
when it wasn't that successful but I
mean we got we got the bounty should we
go and turn this in let's do it here's
some wizard fruit Scotty this he this
Freeman me the same time you ready yep
ready three two one hello witness of
magic rematch ladies and gentlemen
ladies and gentlemen he is a believer
he's a believer in the magic magic and
she thought it says 75 points there on
the sign but actually on this piece of
paper it says 100 so that's good
submitted there it is
folks are you kidding me falsi submitted
her own head ten Enderman ten rabbit
eight pufferfish
oh there's mumbo and there's cub and
there's EF on here where are we I'm over
here
look what's a good place know what have
no way that's without the dragon heads
the sneaky dragon heads dude I don't
know who this green character is he's
the chicken we got we go back up we got
we're still gonna go along with the plan
this is all part of the plan keep keep
er keep it close and then and then we'll
enact our plan all right thank you very
much Skaar sure we zip back
we should yep it's magic editing magic
don't tell Skaar what's what's great is
that Skaar thinks his magic is real and
I'm afraid that is all we have time for
today we've got a lot done we have
claimed some bounties we're well on our
way to winning that giant diamond
jackpot and we have made significant
progress on our base and next episode
I'm hoping to finish off cuz I still got
some more towers to add some more
decorations I didn't quite get there but
I think this is in a state where you can
look at the front and say wow that's a
nice base okay thank you very much for
watching everyone I hope you enjoyed the
video and I shall see you in the next
one good